Guide to The Alfred C. Berol Collection of Lewis Carroll 1845 - 1993 MSS 057
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series 4: Photographs
  - Subseries 4A: Photographs by Charles L. Dodgson.
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Sarah and Benjamin Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[1342] [n.p.][n.d.] 2 full length figures, one seated other standing. Against a cloth backdrop. 5.75 x 4.75, undated; 2028 (Box 8, Folder 589)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence and [Kate] Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] 2 full length figures one seated, one leaning over other to read text in lap. Both in doorway. 5.75 x 4.75, undated; 2029 (Box 8, Folder 590)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Florence Marion Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Two full length figures, seated on striped knit blanket and embracing) 5.75 x 4.5, undated; 2030 (Box 8, Folder 591)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Ellen and Kate Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2372 [n.p.][n.d.] Ellen confers knighthood on Kate. Numbered "2372" on verso. Not mounted on pasteboard. 8.25 x 6.75, undated; 2031 (Box 8, Folder 592)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Ellen and Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number 2372 [n.p.][n.d.] Ellen confers knighthood on Kate. Numbered "2372" on verso. Not mounted on pasteboard. 8.25 x 6.25, undated; 2032 (Box 8, Folder 593)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Sarah and Kate Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] 2 3/4 length figures, one leaning over the shoulder of other reading book. 6.5 x 4.75, undated; 2033 (Box 8, Folder 594)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry, Sarah and Kate Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] 2 3/4 length figures, one leaning over the shoulder of other reading book. 5.75 x 4.75, undated; 2034 (Box 8, Folder 595)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Terry Family Modern Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] Kentish Town, July 15, 1865 At the family"s home in Kentish Town on July 15th, 1865. Not Mounted on Pasteboard. 7.75 x 9.75, 2041 (Box 8, Folder 596)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Croft Rectory, Yorkshire, before 1868 Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 1. 3 x 4, undated; 2042 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Croft Church, Yorkshire Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 2. 2.25 x 3.5, undated; 2043 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Croft Churchyard Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 3. 2.75 x 4, undated; 2044 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Croft Churchyard Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 4. 2.75 x 3.75, undated; 2045 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Interior of Croft Church Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 5. 3 x 3.75, undated; 2046 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of The Study of Croft Rectory Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 6 3.5 x 2.75, undated; 2047 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of The Drawing Room of Croft Rectory Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 7. 3 x 4, undated; 2048 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of National School, Croft Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 8. 3 x 3.75, undated; 2049 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Unidentified photo Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 8 verso, Photo Album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks. 2.75 x 3.75, undated; 2050 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Unidentified photo Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 9. 3.5 x 3.75, undated; 2051 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Unidentified photo Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 9. 2.25 x 3.5, undated; 2052 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - [Dodgson, Charles] [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Agnes Mary Collingwood Grave Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 10. 4 x 5.75, undated; 2053 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Unknown [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Croft Church Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 11. 6 x 8.5, undated; 2054 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Unknown [In photo album with violet cover and leather spine marked "Please return to/ Miss Dodgson/ 12 Albany Terrace/ Leamington Spa/ Warwicks.] Photo of Interior of Croft Church Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Page 12 6 x 8.5, undated; 2055 (Box 8, Folder 597)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Girl Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2224 [n.p.][n.d.] Holding tambourine. Wearing costume and jewelry. Numbered "2224" on verso. 5 x 3.5, undated; 2056 (Box 8, Folder 598)
    - Charles Dodgson Unknown Contemporary Glass Photographic Plate, Negative Number 751 [n.p.][n.d.]. 12 x 10, undated; 2057 (Box 8, Folder 599)
  - Subseries 4B: Photographs by others
    - Marks, Barbara S. Stone Rabbit at St. Mary"s Church, Yorkshire Modern Photographic Print, [n.p.][n.d.]., undated (Box 8, Folder 600)
    - Unknown Photo of Dodgson, Charles Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Numbered "28" on verso, inscribed "M.S, Cunnynghame/ from Lewis Carroll", also numbered II 37 in red pencil. Mounted on pasteboard. 4 x 2.5, undated; 2058 (Box 8, Folder 601)
    - Unknown Photo of Dodgson, Charles Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n] [n.p.][n.d.] Mounted on pasteboard. Inscribed on verso in print at top " to LC from LC." and below in script "for Lizzie Coote/ from CLD/ Mar. 28 1876" and below in a different hand "Author of Alice/in Wonderland.." Mounted on pasteboard. 4 x 2.5, undated; 2061 (Box 8, Folder 602)
    - Unknown Photo of Dodgson, Charles Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n.] [n.p.][n.d.] Mounted on pasteboard. Inscribed on verso in script. At top "CLD" followed by partial numeral beginning "22.." below " Lizzie Coote/ from CLD/ with love /May 1. /78,". 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 2064 (Box 8, Folder 603)
    - Unknown Photo of Dodgson, Charles Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n.] [n.p.][n.d.] In glass. Inscribed on verso "Lucy Wilcox/ from her afftc Cousin/ the Substance, whose/ actinic image is/ on the other side./ June 10 /78" 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 2067 (Box 8, Folder 604)
    - Unknown Photo of Dodgson, Charles Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n.] [n.p.][n.d.] Funeral Card. In folding pasteboard case labeled "In Memoriam" on front, inscribed in pencil on back "From L. Dodgson". 5 x 3, undated; 2070 (Box 8, Folder 605)
    - Unknown Photograph of Ellen Terry Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n.] [n.p.][n.d.] Matted., undated (Box 8, Folder 606)
    - Unknown Photo of Saville Clarkes Dream Play, "Twinkle, Twinkle Little Bat" Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n.] Photo includes Phoebe Carlo. [n.p.][n.d.]. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 2071 (Box 8, Folder 607)
    - Unknown Photo of Saville Clarkes Dream Play, "I Used to be a Real Turtle" Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number[n.n.] [n.p.][n.d.]. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 2072 (Box 8, Folder 608)
- Series 5: Related Materials.
  - Subseries 5A: Advertisements.
    - Courtland"s Department Store Display Magazine., undated (Box 9, Folder 610)
    - International Paper "They"ll Live Forever Through Print and Paper"., undated (Box 9, Folder 611)
  - Subseries 5B: Articles on Dodgson and/or his works.
    - Abeles, Francine "Ranking by Inversion: A Note on C.L. Dodgson" "Determinants and Linear Systems: Charles L. Dodgson"s View" "C.L. Dodgson and Apportionment for Proportional Representation" "Power in Decisions Amongst Multiple Alternatives" "Multiplication in Changing Bases: A Note on Lewis Carroll" Other Miscellaneous articles, undated (Box 9, Folder 612)
    - Ayers, Harry Morgan Lewis Carroll"s Withdrawal of the 1865 Alice., undated (Box 9, Folder 613)
    - Batey, Mavis Alices Adventures in Oxford., undated (Box 9, Folder 614)
    - Black, Duncan "Lewis Carroll and the Cambridge Mathematical School"., undated (Box 9, Folder 615)
    - Bond, W.H. "The Publication of Alice"s Adventures"., undated (Box 9, Folder 616)
    - Goodacre, Selwyn "The Listing of the Snark"., undated (Box 9, Folder 617)
    - Hancock, Cecily Raysor "Musical Notes to the Annotated Alice"., undated (Box 9, Folder 618)
    - Jackson, Joseph Alice as a Book and a Treasure., undated (Box 9, Folder 619)
    - Squire, J.C. Speech at the Opening Ceremony., undated (Box 9, Folder 620)
    - Stafford, Jean "The Jabberwock Anatomized" in The Griffin., undated (Box 9, Folder 621)
    - Swan, Bradford F. Auctioning Alice., undated (Box 9, Folder 622)
    - Vail, R.W.G. Alice in Wonderland :The Manuscript and its Story., undated (Box 9, Folder 623)
    - Van Patten, Nathan The Yerba Buena Press and Some Related Privately Printed Books., undated (Box 9, Folder 624)
    - Warde, B.L. Printing Should Be Invisible., undated (Box 9, Folder 625)
    - Weaver, Warren The India Alice With corrected Ms., proofs, and letters., undated (Box 9, Folder 626)
    - Weaver, Warren Lewis Carroll and a Geometrical Paradox., undated (Box 9, Folder 627)
    - Weaver, Warren Lewis Carroll Correspondence Numbers With corrected Ms., proofs, and letters, undated (Box 9, Folder 628)
    - Weaver, Warren "Lewis Carroll Mathemetician"., undated (Box 9, Folder 629)
  - Subseries 5C:Ephemera.
    - Arcadia Works, London 48 Playing Cards, 2 .5" by 3". In case., undated (Box 9, Folder 630)
    - Arcadia Works, London 48 Playing Cards, 2 .5" by 3". Loose Deck #2., undated (Box 9, Folder 631)
    - Arcadia Works, London 48 Playing Cards, 2 .5" by 3", Loose Deck #3., undated (Box 9, Folder 632)
    - Arcadia Works, London 1 Set Playing Cards, 1 .5" by 2 .75". Loose miniature., undated (Box 9, Folder 633)
    - Dodgson, Charles L. Jabberwocky in Punch Photocopy., undated (Box 10, Folder 634)
    - Dodgson, Charles L. Wonderland Postage Stamp Cases(4), undated (Box 10, Folder 635)
    - Hatch, Ethel Watercolor Untitled [n.p.], [n.d.]., undated (Box 10, Folder 636)
    - Wildridge, T. Tindall "A Lewis Carroll Pageant" Four of a series of six, undated (Box 10, Folder 637)
    - Unknown Christmas Cards Using Alice, undated (Box 10, Folder 638)
    - Unknown Doily [The Walrus and the Carpenter]., undated (Box 10, Folder 639)
    - Unknown Ivory Hatter., undated (Box 10, Folder 640)
    - Unknown The Postage Stamps of Wonderland., undated (Box 10, Folder 641)
    - Unknown Stereoscopic Cards., undated (Box 10, Folder 642)
    - Unknown The Tuck Alice 1926., undated (Box 10, Folder 643)
    - Unknown Gold Watch Marked on back of works "examined by A.S. Bach, 40, Great Russel St., London W.C." Inscribed on inside "Menella from C.L.D. 1888"., undated (Box 10, Folder Vault)
    - Unknown Wonderland postage stamps affixed to Envelopes., undated (Box 10, Folder 644)
    - Various Material on NY Central Park Memorial., undated (Box 10, Folder 645)
  - Subseries 5D: Magazines with Articles on Dodgson and/or his works.
  - Subseries 5E: Newspaper Clippings.
    - Contemporary Newspaper Clippings Obituaries of Dodgson, Charles., undated (Box 10, Folder 646)
    - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings., undated (Box 10, Folder 647)
  - Subseries 5F: Reprints of Dodgson.
    - Dodgson, Charles Address by the Rev. C.L. Dodgson at St. Mary Magdelene Church, St. Leonards-on-Sea., undated (Box 10, Folder 648)
    - Dodgson, Charles Arithmetical Puzzle By Lewis Carroll., undated (Box 10, Folder 649)
    - Dodgson, Charles How the Boots Got Left Behind., undated (Box 10, Folder 650)
    - Dodgson, Charles The Three Cats., undated (Box 10, Folder 651)
  - Subseries 5G: Theater Materials.
    - Henry Savile-Clarke Alice in Wonderland: A Dream Play for Children., undated (Box 10, Folder 652)
    - Miscellaneous Kitty Saville-Clarke Materials 4 Letters and a Performance copy of Henry Saville Clarke"s The Phantom Cutlet., undated (Box 10, Folder 653)
    - Theater Program (photocopy) Alice"s Adventures in Wonderland Daniel Press Original in Daniel Press boxes., undated (Box 10, Folder 654)
    - Theater Programs Eva Le Gallienne Productions "Alice in Wonderland" (1931, 1947, 1982), 1931-1982 (Box 10, Folder 655)
    - Theater Program National Ballet of Canada "Alice"(1986) (Box 10, Folder 656)
    - Theater Program O"Neill, Randall "Alice in Wonderland"(1931) (Box 10, Folder 657)
    - Theater Program Princeton University Players (1954) Princeton University Triangle Club (1953) (Box 10, Folder 658)
- Series 6: Provenance
  - Subseries 6A: Checklists.
    - Checklists of the Berol Collection., undated (Box 11, Folder 659)
  - Subseries 6B:Typescripts.
    - Typescript Dodgson Letters., undated (Box 11, Folder 660)
    - Typescript Dodgson Letters II., undated (Box 11, Folder 661)
  - Subseries 6C1: Correspondence Regarding Collection Materials. (Collection Development and Alfred C. Berol.)
    - Berol Correspondence (multiple letters), undated (Box 11, Folder 662)
    - AB Sandbergs Bohandel to Berol, Alfred., undated (Box 11, Folder ID: 662.1)
    - Bond, W.H. to Berol, Alfred., undated (Box 11, Folder ID: 662.2)
    - Dodgson, F. Menella to Berol, Alfred and Kenneth Berol., undated (Box 11, Folder 663)
    - Drake, M. to Berol, Alfred., undated (Box 11, Folder ID: 663.1)
    - Gibb, Jocelyn to Berol, Alfred., undated (Box 11, Folder ID: 663.2)
    - Gielgud, John / Berol, Afred Correspondence., undated (Box 11, Folder 664)
    - Goldsmith, Alfred to Berol, Alfred., undated (Box 11, Folder 665)
    - Hudson, Derek to Berol, Alfred 666.1 Jackson, [?] to Berol, Alfred., undated (Box 11, Folder 666)
    - Livingston, F. to Berol, Alfred., undated (Box 11, Folder ID: 666.2)
    - Mason, J.F.A. to Berol, Alfred., undated (Box 11, Folder ID: 666.3)
    - Quaritch, Bernard to Berol, Alfred., undated (Box 11, Folder 667)
    - Wright, C.P. to Berol Alfred (w/ reply)., undated (Box 11, Folder ID: 667.1)
  - Subseries 6C2: Correspondence Regarding Collection Materials. (Collection Development and Others).
    - Carter, John misc. Correspondence., undated (Box 11, Folder 668)
    - Clevedon, Douglas to Harrmsworth R.L. (2)., undated (Box 11, Folder ID: 668.1)
    - Collingwood, Grace J., to Messrs Maggs Brothers., undated (Box 11, Folder 669)
    - Fordham, Hallam to Gielgud, Mrs. Kate Terry., undated (Box 11, Folder 670)
    - Madan, Falconer to Strong, H., undated (Box 11, Folder ID: 670.1)
    - Parish and Company to Harmsworth, Sir Leicester., undated (Box 11, Folder 671)
    - Watson, H.D.to Hatch, Evelyn., undated (Box 11, Folder ID: 671.1)
    - Weaver, Warren misc. Correspondence., undated (Box 11, Folder 672)
    - Williams, Sidney to Forman., undated (Box 11, Folder ID: 672.1)
  - Subseries 6D: Provenance Notes
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Duchess of Albany., undated (Box 11, Folder 673)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Argles., undated (Box 11, Folder 674)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Atkinson., undated (Box 11, Folder 675)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Barry., undated (Box 11, Folder 676)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to George Charles Bell., undated (Box 11, Folder 677)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Mrs. C.F. Moberly Bell., undated (Box 11, Folder 678)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Margaret Brough., undated (Box 11, Folder 679)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Mary Collingwood., undated (Box 11, Folder 680)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Sir Robert Collins., undated (Box 11, Folder 681)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Cunnygham., undated (Box 11, Folder 682)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Daniel., undated (Box 11, Folder 683)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Dodgson., undated (Box 11, Folder 684)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Draper., undated (Box 11, Folder 685)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Drury., undated (Box 11, Folder 686)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Beatrice Earle., undated (Box 11, Folder 687)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Feilden., undated (Box 11, Folder 688)
    - Provenance Notes CLD to Ffoulkes., undated (Box 11, Folder 689)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Fletcher, undated (Box 11, Folder 690)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Franklin., undated (Box 11, Folder 691)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, Cld to W. George"s Sons., undated (Box 11, Folder 692)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Girdlestone., undated (Box 11, Folder 693)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Harcourt., undated (Box 11, Folder 694)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Hardman., undated (Box 11, Folder 695)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Holiday., undated (Box 11, Folder 696)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Hunter., undated (Box 11, Folder 697)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Hussey., undated (Box 11, Folder 698)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Jackson., undated (Box 11, Folder 699)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Jebb., undated (Box 11, Folder 700)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Kish., undated (Box 11, Folder 701)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Knight., undated (Box 11, Folder 702)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Langbridge., undated (Box 11, Folder 703)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Prince Leopold., undated (Box 11, Folder 704)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Alice Liddell., undated (Box 11, Folder 705)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Lucy., undated (Box 11, Folder 706)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Mrs. Mallalieu., undated (Box 11, Folder 707)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Martin-Henry., undated (Box 11, Folder 708)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Nicholson., undated (Box 11, Folder 709)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Patmore., undated (Box 11, Folder 710)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Professor., undated (Box 11, Folder 711)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Rivers., undated (Box 11, Folder 712)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Rix., undated (Box 11, Folder 713)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Shute., undated (Box 11, Folder 714)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Stevens, undated (Box 11, Folder 715)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Tidy., undated (Box 11, Folder 716)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Todd., undated (Box 11, Folder 717)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Walters., undated (Box 11, Folder 718)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Ward., undated (Box 11, Folder 719)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Webb., undated (Box 11, Folder 720)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Whatford., undated (Box 11, Folder 721)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Wilcox., undated (Box 11, Folder 722)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, CLD to Yonge., undated (Box 11, Folder 723)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, Harry Furniss to Dodgson., undated (Box 11, Folder 724)
    - Provenance Notes, Letters, Rossetti to Dodgson., undated (Box 11, Folder 725)
    - Provenance Notes, Manuscripts, "A Charade"., undated (Box 11725A, Folder Ovrsz.)
    - Provenance Notes, Manuscripts, "On Pleasure" and "Declamation Read in Hall"., undated (Box 11, Folder 726)
    - Provenance Notes, Photographs, The Terry Family., undated (Box 11, Folder 727)
    - Provenance Notes, Print Material, Eight or Nine Wise Words About Letter Writing"., undated (Box 11, Folder 728)
    - Provenance Notes, Print Material, "An Easter Greeting"., undated (Box 11, Folder 729)
    - Provenance Notes, Print Material, The Wonderland Postage Stamp Case., undated (Box 11, Folder 730)
    - Provenance Notes, Print Material, Berol Collection Songs., undated (Box 11, Folder 731)
    - Provenance Notes, Miscellaneous., undated (Box 11, Folder 732)
  - Subseries 6E Printed Materials. (See Ovrsize Box 14).
    Scope and Contents note
    Articles on Carroll (folders 3-16), and Auction Catalogues (folders 16.1-45)
    - Ayres, H.M., "Carroll"s Withdrawal of the 1865 Alice", Nov. 1934. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Berol, A., "Lanrick - A Goame for 2 Players", 1959. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Blankc, J., "Wonderland Alice", Sept. 15, 1951. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Dickson, S., "The Bulwer-Lytton Collection", 1946. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Evans, L., "the Return of Alic"s", 1965. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Levin, H. "Wonderland Revisited", 1965. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Printing and the Mind of Men, July, 1963 (copy 1). (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Printing and the Mind of Men, July, 1963 (copy 2). (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Shaw, J.M., "The Parodies of Lewis Carroll and their Originals", Dec. 1960. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Weaver, W., "Alice"s Adventures in Wonderland its origin and its author", 1951. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Weaver, W., "The first edition of Alices"s Adventures in Wonderland, a census", 1971 (copy 1). (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Weaver, W., "The first edition of Alices"s Adventures in Wonderland, a census", 1971 (copy 2). (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Weaver, W., "The Mathematical Manuscripts of Lewis Carroll", 1954 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Weaver, W., "The Parrish Collection of Carrolliana", 1956. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - American Art Association Anderson Galleries, Inc., 1938. [folder is labeled "16") (Box 16, Folder ID: 16.1)
    - Betram Rota Ltd., Spring 1958 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Betram Rota Ltd., Summer 1960. (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Blackwell, 1953. (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Christie"s, June 29, 1959; July 1, 1965., 1959,1965 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Christie"s, June 19, 1968. (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Frank Hollings, 1943; 1946. (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries, Oct. 1940. (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Parke-Bernet Galleries, Jan. 1941. (Box 16, Folder 24)